Mss.Ms.Coll.109
American Philosophical Society
- Correspondence, 25.25 linear feet
  - Elperin-Clark, Phyllis, 1992; 1 item (Box 15)
  - Elofson, Shirley, 1961; 1 item (Box 15)
  - Elrod, J. McRee, 1989; 2 items (Box 15)
  - Elten, Jeanne, 1980; 3 items (Box 15)
  - Elwin, Malcolm, 1939-1945; 6 items (Box 15)
  - Emerick, Richard, 1980; 1 item (Box 15)
  - Emmanuel, Reggie, 1976; 1 item (Box 15)
  - Emmel, Edwin D, 1972; 2 items (Box 15)
  - Emmons, Jeanne, 1990; 1 item (Box 15)
  - Engel, Werner H, 1983; 1 item (Box 15)
  - Engerrand, George, 1943; 2 items (Box 15)
  - Engler, Ellie, 1977; 4 items (Box 15)
  - English, Maurice, 1971; 3 items (Box 15)
  - English, O. Spurgeon, 1945-1953; undated; 15 items (Box 15)
  - English, Woodruff J, 1976; 2 items (Box 15)
  - Entract, J.P, 1971; 1972; 2 items (Box 15)
  - Epstein, Jason, 1957; 1 item (Box 15)
  - Epstein, Joseph, 1985; 1987; 4 items (Box 15)
  - Erickson, 1959; 1 item (Box 15)
  - Esalen Institute, 1967; 1968; 11 items (Box 15)
  - Escoll, Morris J, 1969; 1971; 3 items (Box 15)
  - Eskedahl, Solveig Dale, undated; 1 item (Box 15)
  - Espinasse, Margaret, 1939; 2 items (Box 15)
  - Etzioni, Amitm, 1969; 1 item (Box 15)
  - Eugene McCarthy Political Campaign, 1968; undated; 9 items (Box 15)
  - Evans, Bergen, 1943-1965; undated; 93 items (Box 15)
  - Evans, Herbert M, 1938; 2 items (Box 15)
  - Evans, Owen R, 1966; 3 items (Box 15)
  - Eve, Martin, 1962; 1 item (Box 15)
  - Everett, John R, 1972; 1973; 2 items (Box 15)
  - Everstine, Louis, 1961-1966; 8 items (Box 15)
  - Faber, M.D., 1982; 4 items (Box 16)
  - Fadiman, Clifton, 1957; 1 item (Box 16)
  - Faggen, Robert, 1981; 2 items (Box 16)
  - Fahy, J. Carter, 1976; 2 items (Box 16)
  - Fairbanks, Gertrude, 1953; undated; 12 items (Box 16)
  - Fairbanks, William L, 1981; 1 item (Box 16)
  - Fairchild, H.P, 1956; 1 item (Box 16)
  - Fairchild, Johnson E, 1958; 1 item (Box 16)
  - Fallin, Richard, 1964; 2 items (Box 16)
  - Fano, Maria Gina, 1930; 1 item (Box 16)
  - Farb, Peter, 1977-1978; 3 items (Box 16)
  - Farber, Ajon F, 1975; 1 item (Box 16)
  - Farlow, Jay, 1971; 2 items (Box 16)
  - Farmer, Kitty, 1994; 1 item (Box 16)
  - Farnsworth, Al, 1974; 1 item (Box 16)
  - Farnsworth, Richard, 1972; 1 item (Box 16)
  - Farnsworth, Shirley, undated; 1 item (Box 16)
  - Farquhar, Samual T, 1941; 1 item (Box 16)
  - Farrar, C.B, 1960; 2 items (Box 16)
  - Farrington, B, 1939; 6 items (Box 16)
  - Fassett, F.G, 1944; 1 item (Box 16)
  - Faulconer, Corinne, 1976; 1 item (Box 16)
  - Faust, Elizabeth, 1966; 1 item (Box 16)
  - Faxon, Prudence, 1998; 2 items (Box 16)
  - Feazel, Sue, 1986; 1 item (Box 16)
  - Federative Committee for Anatomical Terminology, 1994; 1 item (Box 16)
  - Federici, Nora, 1967; 1 item (Box 16)
  - Federman, Daniel D, 1973; 1 item (Box 16)
  - Feinman, E. Antonia, 1981; 1 item (Box 16)
  - Fejos, Paul, 1955; 1956; 2 items (Box 16)
  - Feldman, Esther, 1980; 1 item (Box 16)
  - Felson, Benjamin, 1983; 1 item (Box 16)
  - Feman, Sanford N, undated; 1 item (Box 16)
  - Fenig, Ethel C, undated; 1 item (Box 16)
  - Fenwick, Millicent, 1978-1981; undated; 54 items (Box 16)
  - Ferguson, Charles, 1966; 1 item (Box 16)
  - Fernandez, James, 1980-1992; undated; 10 items (Box 16)
  - Fibush, Esther, 1978; 1 item (Box 16)
  - Field, Henry, 1931-1978; 4 items (Box 16)
  - Filsinger, Sara Teasdale, 1930; 3 items (Box 16)
  - Finch, Henry A, 1950-1953; 2 items (Box 16)
  - Findlay, Trevor, 1988; 1 item (Box 16)
  - Finger, Gerrie, 1968; 1 item (Box 16)
  - Finkelstein, M.I, 1940; 2 items (Box 16)
  - Finlay, John H, 1942; 1 item (Box 16)
  - Firth, Raymond, 1951-1959; 7 items (Box 16)
  - Fisher, Craig, 1969; 1 item (Box 16)
  - Fisher, Helen, 1981; 2 items (Box 16)
  - Fishler, Bennett, 1977; 1 item (Box 16)
  - Fishman, Harvey and Barbara, 1982; 1983; undated; 17 items (Box 16)
  - Fishman, William, 1977-1990; 3 items (Box 16)
  - Fiske, Peter, 1979; 1 item (Box 16)
  - Fitch, Robert, 1957; 1 item (Box 16)
  - Fite, George L, 1966; 2 items (Box 16)
  - Fitz, Reginald, 1946; 1 item (Box 16)
  - Fitz-Gibbon, Bernice, 1967; 1 item (Box 16)
  - Flack, Harvey & Joyce, 1957-1993; undated; 34 items (Box 16)
  - Flanagan, Dennis, 1950-1979; undated; 4 items (Box 16)
  - Flemming, Edward Willis, 1990; 1 item (Box 16)
  - Fleure, H.J, 1938-1954; 2 items (Box 16)
  - Flint, Suzan K, 1985; 1 item (Box 16)
  - Flugel, John Carl, 1955; 2 items (Box 16)
  - Fodor, Nandor, 1951; 1 item (Box 16)
  - Foldvary, Gabor Z, 1980; 1 item (Box 16)
  - Ford, Edward, 1937; 1 item (Box 16)
  - Forman, Norm, 1979; 2 items (Box 16)
  - Forsblad, Susan, 1995; 1 item (Box 16)
  - Forster, Edward, 1939-1945; undated; 5 items (Box 16)
  - Forster, John, 1937; 3 items (Box 16)
  - Fosca, Gerald, 1981; 1 item (Box 17)
  - Fosdick, Raymond, 1942-1943; 6 items (Box 17)
  - Fox, Elizabeth, 1968-1980; undated; 3 items (Box 17)
  - Fox, Jack, 1958; 2 items (Box 17)
  - Fox, Michael W, 1984; 1 item (Box 17)
  - Fox, Richard G, 1994; 3 items (Box 17)
  - Fox, Robin, 1968-1998; November 7; February 25; 6 items (Box 17)
  - Fox, Sidney, 1981-1984; 3 items (Box 17)
  - Fox, T.F, 1961; 1 item (Box 17)
  - Foyle, Vilma Grbac, 1983; 1 item (Box 17)
  - Fraccaro, Marco, 1968; 1 item (Box 17)
  - Frair, Wayne, 1969; 1 item (Box 17)
  - Frances, Juanita, 1956; 1 item (Box 17)
  - Francis, Arlene, 1968; 1 item (Box 17)
  - Frank, Lawrence, 1950-1960; 5 items (Box 17)
  - Frank, Leonard Roy, 1991; 3 items (Box 17)
  - Franklin, J. Stuart, 1988; 1 item (Box 17)
  - Franklin, Kenneth, 1943-1944; 3 items (Box 17)
  - Franta, Jaroslav, 1977; 1 item (Box 17)
  - Frederick, Ted, 1982; 2 items (Box 17)
  - Fredericson, Emil, 1951; 1 item (Box 17)
  - Fredrickson, George M, 1972; 1 item (Box 17)
  - Freeman, Derek, 1936-1995; undated; 51 items (Box 17)
  - Freeman, Samuel D, 1972; 1 item (Box 17)
  - Fremon, Jane, 1993; 1 item (Box 17)
  - Freer, Neil, 1988; 1 item (Box 17)
  - Fremon, Jane, 1993 (Box 17)
  - Fremont-Smith, Frank, 1941-1951; 4 items (Box 17)
  - Freshney, Emiy, 1982; 1 item (Box 17)
  - Freud, Oliver, 1948; 1 item (Box 17)
  - Freud, W. Ernst, 1980; 1982; 2 items (Box 17)
  - Fried, Morton, 1965-1968; 3 item (Box 17)
  - Fried, Ralph, 1965; 1 item (Box 17)
  - Friedland, Ronald, 1971; 1 item (Box 17)
  - Friedman, Maurice, 1967; 1 item (Box 17)
  - Friedman, Stanley, 1976; 1 item (Box 17)
  - Fritchman, Stephen, 1963; 1 item (Box 17)
  - Froehlich, Edwina, 1977; 1 item (Box 17)
  - Fromm, Erich, 1948-1956; 14 items (Box 17)
  - Fromm-Reichmann, Frieda, 1952; 1 item (Box 17)
  - Frumkin, Robert M, 1955; 1 item (Box 17)
  - Fry, C.B, 1988; December; 2 items (Box 17)
  - Fry, Edward, 1969-1982; 5 items (Box 17)
  - Fry, T.C, 1970; 1971; 2 items (Box 17)
  - Fuhrman, Martha, 1981; 1 item (Box 17)
  - Fuller, Justine, 1947; 5 items (Box 17)
  - Fulton, James Street, 1955; 1 item (Box 17)
  - Fulton, John F, 1935-1955; 38 items (Box 17)
  - Fulton, Richard, 1970-1972; 4 items (Box 17)
  - Furnas, J.C, 1956; 3 items (Box 17)
  - F-Misc, 1973-1982; undated; 11 items (Box 17)
  - G-Misc, 1962-1996; 33 items (Box 19)
  - Gach, John, 1989; 1 item (Box 18)
  - Gajdusek, Carleton, undated; 1 item (Box 18)
    Possibly by D. Carleton Gajdusek. Labeled by Montagu as from "Carleton J Gadjusek."
  - Galbraith, John Kenneth, 1977; 1 item (Box 18)
  - Galdston, Iago, 1944-1956; 3 items (Box 18)
  - Gallagher, Buell, 1952; 1 item (Box 18)
  - Galt, Alfreda, 1995; 1 item (Box 18)
  - Gambale, George, 1968; 1 item (Box 18)
  - Gamow, Barbara, 1968; 1 item (Box 18)
  - Gan, Steven, 1983; 1 item (Box 18)
  - Gardiner, Margaret, 1967; 1 item (Box 18)
  - Gardner, James A, 1972; 4 items (Box 18)
  - Gardner, Lytt A, 1969; 1971; 2 items (Box 18)
  - Gardner, Martin, 1958; 1 item (Box 18)
  - Garn, Stanley M, 1959; 1960; 2 items (Box 18)
  - Garey, Arthur, 1976; 2 items (Box 18)
  - Garganta, A.A, 1981; 1 item (Box 18)
  - Garland, Keldyn, 1994; 1 item (Box 18)
  - Garner, Les R, 1983; 1991; 4 items (Box 18)
  - Garre, Walter, 1978; 3 items (Box 18)
  - Gartler, Stanley, 1987; 1 item (Box 18)
  - Gates, Henry Louis Jr, 1985; 1 item (Box 18)
  - Gates, Laura Ruggles, 1970; 1 item (Box 18)
  - Gates, R. Ruggles, 1949-1960; 3 items (Box 18)
  - Gavin, Jim, 1997; 1 item (Box 18)
  - Gebo, Norman J, 1997; 1 item (Box 18)
  - Gedda, Luigi, 1952-1978; undated; 4 items (Box 18)
  - Geertz, Clifford, 1981; 1 item (Box 18)
  - Geismar, Maxwell, 1960-1962; 3 items (Box 18)
  - Gelb, Barbara, 1973; 1 item (Box 18)
  - Geldard, Frank, 1970; 1 item (Box 18)
  - Gelgy Pharmaceuticals, 1968; 1969; 4 items (Box 18)
  - Gell, Jonathan, 1977; 1 item (Box 18)
  - Geltman, Manny, 1967; 5 items (Box 18)
  - Genevie, Louis, 1986; 1 item (Box 18)
  - Genorese, E.D, 1963; 1 item (Box 18)
  - Genoves, Santiago, 1965; 1970; 2 items (Box 18)
  - Gentry, W. Doyle, undated; 1 item (Box 18)
  - Genung, Lin Orrin, 1977; 1 item (Box 18)
  - Georgantas, Patricia, 1995; 1 item (Box 18)
  - Gerard, Ralph W, 1965; 6 items (Box 18)
  - Gerhardi, William, 1964; 1 item (Box 18)
  - Gersten, Raoul, 1971; undated; 5 items (Box 18)
  - Gervasi, Tom & Eugene, 1965; 1967; 2 items (Box 18)
  - Gery, Lisa, 1989; 1 item (Box 18)
  - Geyl, Peter, 1961; 3 items (Box 18)
  - Gibbons, Gerard, 1970-1980; 5 items (Box 18)
  - Gibbons, Reginald, 1995; 1 item (Box 18)
  - Giblett, Eloise, 1959; 1 item (Box 18)
  - Gibson, Connie, 1987; 1 item (Box 18)
  - Gieryna, Betty, 1981; 1 item (Box 18)
  - Gilbertson, Pat, 1989; 2 items (Box 18)
  - Gill, R.D, 1972; 1 item (Box 18)
  - Gillette, Paul J, 1971; 2 items (Box 18)
  - Gilliland, William, 1951-1958; 2 items (Box 18)
  - Gillispie, Charles, 1983; 1984; 2 items (Box 18)
  - Gillooly, Robert, 1990; 1993; 1994; 7 items (Box 18)
  - Gilman, William, 1969-1970; 3 items (Box 18)
  - Gimbutas, Marija, 1988-1993; 10 items (Box 18)
  - Gindi, Karyn, 1992; 1 item (Box 18)
  - Ginsberg, M, 1968-1970; 4 items (Box 18)
  - Ginsburgh, Ellen, 1971; 1 item (Box 18)
  - Ginzburg, Ralph, 1962-1963; 3 items (Box 18)
  - Gladwin, Thomas, 1950; 1 item (Box 18)
  - Glaeser, Marion, 1967; 1 item (Box 18)
  - Glantz, Medora, 1978; 2 items (Box 18)
  - Glass, Bentley, 1952; 1954; 2 items (Box 18)
  - Glass, Marion, 1971; 1 item (Box 18)
  - Glasser, Otto, 1941-1948; 5 items (Box 18)
  - Gobetz, Edward, 1986; 1 item (Box 18)
  - Goble, Frank, 1970; 1 item (Box 18)
  - Godfrey, Marion, 1947; 1 item (Box 18)
  - Godine, David, 1975-1981; undated; 9 items (Box 18)
  - Godsey, Margie, 1983; 1 item (Box 18)
  - Godyaew, Alexey, 1969; 1 item (Box 18)
  - Goebel, Paul, 1983; 1 item (Box 18)
  - Golden, Daniel L, 1973; 1976; 2 items (Box 18)
  - Golden, Harry, 1958; 1 item (Box 18)
  - Goldman, Dave, undated; 2 items (Box 18)
  - Goldsby, Gilmer, 1968; 1 item (Box 18)
  - Goldsmith, Samuel, 1956; 1957; 2 items (Box 18)
  - Goldstein, Kurt, 1939-1941; 3 items (Box 18)
  - Goldstein, Marcus, 1940-1998; March 7; 50 items (Box 19)
  - Gollattscheck, James, 1977; 1 item (Box 18)
  - Goode, William J, undated; 1 item (Box 18)
  - Goodman, Alan, 1994; 6 items (Box 18)
  - Goodman, L. Landon, 1957; 1 item (Box 18)
  - Goodman, Paul, 1950; 2 items (Box 18)
  - Goodwin, Polly, 1965; 1 item (Box 18)
  - Gooneratne, Yasmine, 1971; 2 items (Box 18)
  - Gordimer, Nadine, 1988; 1992; 2 items (Box 19)
  - Gordon, Cyris, 1957; 1 item (Box 19)
  - Gordon, Judy, 1986; 2 items (Box 19)
  - Gordon, Richard J, 1971-1972; 3 items (Box 19)
  - Gorham, Penny, 1978; 1 item (Box 19)
  - Gorney, Roderic, 1967-1999; 102 items (Box 19)
  - Gornick, Hannah, undated; 1 item (Box 19)
  - Gossage, Henry Luck, 1963-1968; 7 items (Box 19)
  - Gossage, Howard, 1967; 1 item (Box 19)
  - Gottlieb, Gilbert, 1985-1988; 7 items (Box 19)
  - Gottlieb, Marc, 1992; 2 items (Box 19)
  - Goudge, T.A, 1957; 1 item (Box 19)
  - Gould, Ben, 1956; 1 item (Box 19)
  - Gould, Natalie, 1994; 1995; 2 items (Box 19)
  - Gould, Steven Jay, 1974-1992; 28 items (Box 19)
  - Goyen, William, 1970; 1 item (Box 19)
  - Grant, Jane, 1955; 1960; 2 items (Box 19)
  - Grant, Stephanie Ogden, 1982; 1 item (Box 19)
  - Graubard, Mark, 1940-1944; 5 items (Box 19)
  - Graves, Nelson, 1963; 1 item (Box 19)
  - Graves, William W, 1938; 1 item (Box 19)
  - Grayling, A.C, 1998; 1 item (Box 19)
  - Graziano, Eugene, 1987; 1 item (Box 19)
  - Greeley, David, 1963; 1 item (Box 19)
  - Green, C.W, 1969; 2 items (Box 19)
  - Green, Dave, 1945; 1 item (Box 19)
  - Green, Karen, 1989; 1 item (Box 19)
  - Green, Victor, 1975; 1 item (Box 19)
  - Greenan, Lassie, 1977; 1 item (Box 19)
  - Greenbaum, Henry, 1971; 1 item (Box 19)
  - Greenberg, Evelyn, 1969; 1 item (Box 19)
  - Greenbie, Barrie, 1982; 1 item (Box 19)
  - Greenblat, Edward, 1998; 1 item (Box 19)
  - Greene, Elliot, 1989; 1 item (Box 19)
  - Greene, Janet S, 1952; 1 item (Box 19)
  - Greene, John, 1954; 1 item (Box 19)
  - Greene, Rosalind (Mrs. Henry Copley), 1957-1971; undated; 22 items (Box 19)
  - Greengard, Richard, 1978; 1 item (Box 19)
  - Greengold, Myron, 1963; 1 item (Box 19)
  - Greer, Rebecca, 1971; 10 items (Box 19)
  - Gregory,Willliam K, 1928-1971; 23 items (Box 19)
  - Grenier, Louie, 1978; 1 item (Box 19)
  - Greulich, Richard, 1979; 1982; 2 items (Box 19)
  - Greulich, William, 1959; 1 item (Box 19)
  - Griffin, Susan, 1989; 1 item (Box 19)
  - Groch, Judie, 1968-1970; 3 items (Box 19)
  - Grolier, Eric de, 1979; 1 item (Box 19)
  - Grooms, A.D, 1977; 1 item (Box 19)
  - Groot, Kenneth, 1977; 1 item (Box 19)
  - Gross, Hugo, 1951; 2 items (Box 19)
  - Gross, Leonard, undated; 1 item (Box 19)
  - Grosshans, John, 1978; 1 item (Box 19)
  - Grosskurth, Phyllis, 1988; 2 items (Box 19)
  - Grossman, Richard L, 1969; 1 item (Box 19)
  - Grove, Marion, 1925; 2 items (Box 19)
  - Grow, Natalie, 1988; 1 item (Box 19)
  - Gruelich, W.W, 1939; 1 item (Box 19)
  - Gruen, Arno, 1985-1987; 14 items (Box 19)
  - Gruman, Gerald, 1957; 1 item (Box 19)
  - Guillaume, Marie, 1982; 2 items (Box 19)
  - Guillon, Peg, 1967; 1 item (Box 19)
  - Gunther, A.E, 1940; 2 items (Box 19)
  - Gunther, R.T, 1936; 1 item (Box 19)
  - Gutierrez, Ernie, 1981; 1 item (Box 19)
  - Guttmacher, Alan, 1960-1964; 5 items (Box 19)
  - Haas, Jengiz, 1984; 1 item (Box 20)
  - Haddon, Dorothy, 1997; 1 item (Box 20)
  - Hadkiss, Joan, 1972; 1 item (Box 20)
  - Haggerty, Eugene, 1987; 2 items (Box 20)
  - Hahnemann Medical College and Hospital of Philadelphia, 1949; 3 items (Box 20)
  - Haire, Doris, 1979; 1 item (Box 20)
  - Halberstein, R.A, 1979; 1 item (Box 20)
  - Haldane, J.B.S, 1945; 1951; 3 items (Box 20)
  - Hale, Karen, 1984; 1 item (Box 20)
  - Hall, E.T. Jr, 1948-1991; 10 items (Box 20)
  - Hall, Elizabeth, 1966; 1 item (Box 20)
  - Hall, Wallace, 1966; 2 items (Box 20)
  - Haller, John S, 1972; 1 item (Box 20)
  - Halliday, R.J, 1980; 1 item (Box 20)
  - Halloway, Ralph, 1967-1984; 29 items (Box 22)
  - Hallowell, A. Irving, 1937-1961; undated; 9 items (Box 20)
  - Hallowell, Christopher, 1980; 1 item (Box 20)
  - Halpin, William C, 1982; 1 item (Box 20)
  - Halsey, Margaret, 1953; 1963; 2 items (Box 20)
  - Halsteah, Beverly, 1982; 1 item (Box 20)
  - Hambler, W.D, 1946; 1 item (Box 20)
  - Hamiltern, Evelyn, January 5; 1 item (Box 20)
  - Hamilton, James B, 1969; 1 item (Box 20)
  - Hamilton, Jean Marie, 1983; 6 items (Box 20)
  - Hamlin, Margaret, 1953; 1 item (Box 20)
  - Hamm, Virginia, 1989; 1 item (Box 20)
  - Hampden-Turner, C.M, 1970; 1 item (Box 20)
  - Hand, Greg, 1995; 1 item (Box 20)
  - Handel, Ari, 1990; 1 item (Box 20)
  - Handley, Hedda, 1939; 2 items (Box 20)
  - Handlin, Oscar, 1964-1990; 22 items (Box 20)
  - Hanig, Josh, 1988; 1 item (Box 20)
  - Hankoff, L.D, 1976; 1 item (Box 20)
  - Hanks, John T, 1934; 1 item (Box 20)
  - Hanna, Judith Lynne, 1980-1995; undated; 10 items (Box 20)
  - Hanna, Tam, 1976-1987; 4 items (Box 20)
  - Hansell & Post, 1984; 17 items (Box 20)
    Correspondence relating to Montagu's participation in the Shockley v. Cox Inc Enterprises and Roger Witherspoon Trial.
  - Hanson, Barbie, 1982; 1 item (Box 20)
  - Hanson, Jarice, 1984-1994; 22 items (Box 20)
  - Haraway, Donna, 1990; 1 item (Box 20)
  - Harburg, E.Y, 1978; 1 item (Box 20)
  - Hardin, D, 1992; 1 item (Box 20)
  - Hardin, Garrett, 1959-1983; 4 items (Box 20)
  - Harding, Laura, 1979; 1 item (Box 20)
  - Harding, Raymond, 1964; 2 items (Box 20)
  - Hargadon, Fred, undated; 1 item (Box 20)
  - Hargrove, Bennett, December 16; 1 item (Box 20)
  - Hari, Kenneth, 1970; 3 item (Box 20)
  - Harlow, Margaret, 1970; 1 item (Box 20)
  - Harms, Ernest, 1965; 1 item (Box 20)
  - Harnad, Stevan, 1982-1986; 3 items (Box 20)
  - Haronian, Frank, 1970; 1 item (Box 20)
  - Harper, Rosamond, January 29; 1 item (Box 20)
  - Haring, Douglas, 1947; 1 item (Box 20)
  - Harrington, Charles, 1978; 1 item (Box 20)
  - Harrington, Donald Szantho, 1974; 1 item (Box 20)
  - Harrington, M.R, 1956; 1 item (Box 20)
  - Harris, Edward F, 1971; 1 item (Box 20)
  - Harris, Leon A, 1964; 1 item (Box 20)
  - Harris, Marvin, 1974-1979; 6 items (Box 20)
  - Harris, Nancy, 1972; 1 item (Box 20)
  - Harris, T. George, 1971; 1 item (Box 20)
  - Harrison, G. Ainsworth, 1962; 1 item (Box 20)
  - Harrison, Michelle, 1982; 1 item (Box 20)
  - Harrison, R.J, 1952-1959; 3 items (Box 20)
  - Hart, Donn V, 1944; 1 item (Box 20)
  - Hart, Jude, 1978; 2 items (Box 20)
  - Hart-Davis, Rupert, 1956-1963; 5 items (Box 20)
  - Hartley, Caroline, 1997; 7 items (Box 20)
  - Hartley, Wesley, 1993; 1 item (Box 20)
  - Hartman, Carl, 1935-1942; undated; 6 items (Box 20)
  - Hartman, Robert S, 1949; 1 item (Box 20)
  - Hartshorne, Charles, 1995; 2 items (Box 20)
  - Harty, Harry L, 1985; 1 item (Box 20)
  - Harvard Faculty Club, 1983; 1 item (Box 20)
  - Harvard University, 1943-1945; 14 items (Box 20)
  - Harvard-Watts, John, 1966; 1971; 2 items (Box 20)
  - Haskell, Edward, 1948; 1 item (Box 20)
  - Hatch, Robert, 1957; 2 items (Box 20)
  - Hatry, Patricia, 1968-1970; 2 items (Box 20)
  - Hauben, Robert, 1979; 2 items (Box 20)
  - Haupt, H.C, 1984; 1 item (Box 20)
  - Haverstock, Nathan, 1976; 1 item (Box 20)
  - Hawkes, Jacquetta, 1957-1958; 4 items (Box 20)
  - Hawkes, William E, 1972; 1 item (Box 20)
  - Hawkins, Janet S, 1985; 1 item (Box 20)
  - Hay, Michaela, 1975; 1 item (Box 20)
  - Hayakawa, Don & Marge, undated; 1 item (Box 20)
  - Haydn, Hiram, 1963; 1 item (Box 20)
  - Hayes, Charles F, 1971; 1 item (Box 20)
  - Hayes, H.R., 1965; 1972; 2 items (Box 20)
  - Hayes, Helen, 1954; 1 item (Box 20)
  - Hayes, Natalie, 1981; 1982; 2 items (Box 20)
  - Hayes, Richard A, 1976-1977; 6 items (Box 20)
  - Hays, James D, 1972; 1 item (Box 20)
  - Haywfawa, Don, 1953; 1956; 2 items (Box 20)
  - Heard, Gerald, 1929-1955; 3 items (Box 21)
  - Heath, Susan, 1978; 1 item (Box 21)
  - Hechinger, Fred, 1965;1979; 2 items (Box 21)
  - Hedden, Norma, 1976; 1 item (Box 21)
  - Heeb, Patricia, 1988; 2 items (Box 21)
  - Heffernan, Roy J, 1966; 1 item (Box 21)
  - Heffner, Richard, 1982; 1 item (Box 21)
  - Heilbronn, Lisa, undated; 1 item (Box 21)
  - Heindel, Richard, 1951; 1 item (Box 21)
  - Heitert, Peggy, 1977; 1 item (Box 21)
  - Heller, Sharon, 1988-1997; 4 items (Box 21)
  - Helmuth, Herman, 1970-1974; 3 items (Box 21)
  - Hemley, Cecil, 1957-1959; 3 items (Box 21)
  - Henderson, Harry, 1964; 1 item (Box 21)
  - Hendrix, Dean A, 1981; 1 item (Box 21)
  - Henrikson, Bob, undated; 1 item (Box 21)
  - Henry, Jules, 1963-1965; 8 items (Box 21)
  - Henshaw, George, 1975; 1 item (Box 21)
  - Hepburn, Katharine, 1950;1990; 2 items (Box 21)
  - Heppner, C.A, 1978; 1 item (Box 21)
  - Herchul, A, 1950; 1 item (Box 21)
  - Hering, Ron, undated; 4 items (Box 21)
  - Herman, David, 1982; 1996; undated; 16 items (Box 21)
  - Herren, Carol, 1981; 1 item (Box 21)
  - Herrick, C. Judson, 1953-1956; 12 items (Box 21)
  - Herrick, Sal, 1984; undated; 4 items (Box 21)
  - Herrington, Alice, 1971; 1 item (Box 21)
  - Hershey, Daniel, 1983; 1984; 2 items (Box 21)
  - Herskovitz, Melville, 1942-1952; 4 items (Box 21)
  - Herzog, George, 1939; 2 items (Box 21)
  - Heschel, Abraham, 1966; 1 item (Box 21)
  - Heuving, Ralph, 1978; 1 item (Box 21)
  - Heyl, Bert, undated; 1 item (Box 21)
  - Heyn, Dalma, 1978; 1 item (Box 21)
  - Hibbs, Ben, 1954; 1 item (Box 21)
  - Hickman, Marie, 1980; 1 item (Box 21)
  - Hicks, Lewis W, 1975; 1 item (Box 21)
  - Hiebert, Erwin, 1974-1975; 3 items (Box 21)
  - Hiernaux, Jean, 1965; 2 items (Box 21)
  - Hiers, Becky, 1989; 1 item (Box 21)
  - Hightower, Jamake, 1985-1991; 13 items (Box 21)
  - Hilberg, Raul, 1968; 1985; 2 items (Box 21)
  - Hill, Joan, 1986; 1 item (Box 21)
  - Hill, John, 1982-1986; 5 items (Box 21)
  - Hill, Patrick, 1995; 1 item (Box 21)
  - Hill, W.C.Osman, 1939-1943; 3 items (Box 21)
  - Hilllman, M, 1947; 1 item (Box 21)
  - Himes, Norman E, 1936; 3 items (Box 21)
  - Hine, James R, 1978; 1 item (Box 21)
  - Hirsch, Laura Grace, 1959; 1 item (Box 21)
  - Hirschfeld, Gerhard, 1957; 1 item (Box 21)
  - Hirschhorn, Kurt, undated; 1 item (Box 21)
  - Hissong, Deborah, 1978; 5 items (Box 21)
  - Hitchcock, Patricia, 1981; 1 item (Box 21)
  - Hitt, Jack, undated; 1 item (Box 21)
  - Hobbs, Wally, 1983;1984; 2 items (Box 21)
  - Hobler, Herbert W, 1989; 1 item (Box 21)
  - Hockett, Charles F, 1963-1966; 5 items (Box 21)
  - Hocking, E, 1955; 1 item (Box 21)
  - Hoebel, E Adamson, 1967; 1 item (Box 21)
  - Hoel, Sigurd, 1936; 1 item (Box 21)
  - Hoffman, Betty, 1971; 1 item (Box 21)
  - Hoffman, Eve, 1989; 2 items (Box 21)
  - Hoffman, Hallock, 1988; 1 item (Box 21)
  - Hoffmann, Eleonor, 1978; 4 items (Box 21)
  - Hogarth, William, 1982; 2 items (Box 21)
  - Hogben, C, 1941-1962; 5 items (Box 21)
  - Hohmuth,Eileen, undated; 1 item (Box 21)
  - Hoiriis, Lelia B, 1978; 1 item (Box 21)
  - Hoke, Bob, 1969; 2 items (Box 21)
  - Hollamd John, 1969; 1 item (Box 22)
  - Holland, Jimmie, 1973; 1 item (Box 22)
  - Holleman. Linda, 1985; 1 item (Box 22)
  - Hollinshead, Byron, 1983; 1 item (Box 22)
  - Hollitscher, Walter, 1971-1984; 6 items (Box 22)
  - Holloway, Ralph, 1967-1984; 21 items (Box 22)
  - Holmes, Helen, 1980; 1 item (Box 22)
  - Holmes, Kenneth, 1990; 1 item (Box 22)
  - Holmes, Steven, undated; 1 item (Box 22)
  - Holob, Rose, 1971; 1 item (Box 22)
  - Holst, Gustan, undated; 1 item (Box 22)
  - Holton, Gerald, 1979; 1 item (Box 22)
  - Honda, Masaaki, 1983-1985; 8 items (Box 22)
  - Hooton, Earnest, A, 1936-1950; 17 items (Box 22)
  - Howells, W.W, 1939-1995; 7 items (Box 22)
  - Huxley, Julian, 1958-1975; 11 items (Box 22)
  - Honetschlager, Mary A, 1984; 1 item (Box 22)
  - Hopkins, Prynce, 1960-1969; 9 items (Box 22)
  - Hopper, Paul, 1980; 1 item (Box 22)
  - Horowitz, Susan V, 1978; 1 item (Box 22)
  - Horrocks, John E, 1964; 1 item (Box 22)
  - Horwitz, June, 1958; 2 items (Box 22)
  - Hosken, Fran P, 1975-1984; 7 items (Box 22)
  - Houstoun, Marion F, 1971; 3 items (Box 22)
  - Howard, Edgar B, 1938; 1 item (Box 22)
  - Howard, Jane, 1979; 1984; 2 items (Box 22)
  - Howard, Toni, 1961-1972; 7 items (Box 22)
  - Howe, W.T.H, 1936; undated; 3 items (Box 22)
  - Howell, Clark, 1959-1970; undated; 5 items (Box 22)
  - Howell, Warren R, 1965-1982; 3 items (Box 22)
  - Howells, John G, 1965-1966; 3 items (Box 22)
  - Howse, Jeffrey, 1984; 1 item (Box 22)
  - Hoyt, John A, 1972; 1 item (Box 22)
  - Hrdlicka, A, 1941; 1 item (Box 22)
  - Hren, Cynthia, 1982-1985; 9 items (Box 22)
  - Hrisch, Jerry, 1981; 1 item (Box 22)
  - Hsu, Francis, L.K, 1953; 1 item (Box 22)
  - Hsu, T.C, 1959; 1 item (Box 22)
  - Hubbard, Earl (Mrs.), 1967; 1 item (Box 22)
  - Hudson, Frederic M., 1976-1977; 6 items (Box 22)
  - Hudson, James, 1978; 1 item (Box 22)
  - Huffman, John W, 1978-1982; 9 items (Box 22)
  - Huffmann, 1980; 1 item (Box 22)
  - Hughes, Dorothy, 1981; 1982; 2 items (Box 22)
  - Hughes, Eugene, M, 1984; 1 item (Box 22)
  - Hughes, Langston, 1965; 1 item (Box 22)
  - Hughes, William, 1978; 1 item (Box 22)
  - Hulbert, Ann, 1980; 1 item (Box 22)
  - Hullfish, H. Gordon, 1954; 1 item (Box 22)